Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the grand finals of the Intire Extreme Masters live from Type.
We're here at the Type Game Show at the Type Trade Centre and we're all excited for
the next Besta 7 that we have ahead of us as two great players go head to head to see
who will be crown champion of the Intire Extreme Masters here in Type.
The Formula Desk is pig, Todd and Galaris.
We've had an 8-man invitation or started yesterday.
We've now got two players remaining.
We have the two-time world champion in SOS going up against Bionna player
that we haven't seen in a couple of years and all of a sudden he shot to the top of the rankings
on the internet and he's now come to this tournament for the first time in a long time
attending a tournament internationally. He's made it to the grand finals, Claris.
And before we get to be on, may I just say I loved that PPP.
It was great fun. I love disruptors. They're beautiful.
There you go. I don't know. That's an honest thing.
Thank you, Claris.
Made it to the grand finals. Two great plays epic.
Yeah, of course. I mean, these guys are both worked hard to get here.
SOS has been showing us determination and ability to just kill people in crazy situations.
So I think it's cool that Bionna's lived up to the hype so far and I think now he gets the
final boss test. Can you make it past the two-time world champion, the best player in Hots?
Like, can you do that? It's going to be a hard run, but historically he's done pretty okay.
It's a toll feat.
Absolutely. It feels like the gruelol matchup of the new guy,
so to speak, the returning guy in Bionna who used to be considered very highly, maybe not one of
the absolute best, necessarily, but used to be one of those guys that whoever had to face him
probably thought it was going to be a pretty tough match no matter who you were against SOS.
I don't think these guys need any introduction. One of the absolute best players in the world,
one of the highest earners in StarCraft 2 and just one of the best protests all together.
Yeah. One of the most fascinating players to watch as well because he does mix it up so much.
And he is so creative. I think that's something we rarely see someone like that be super consistent.
And I mean, you could argue that SOS hasn't been that consistent himself, but when you put two world,
two Blizzcon championships and an IEM world championship together, it's a pretty high level of
consistency and most importantly of all, he's the master of tearing his opponent apart.
You know, he's the guy who always finds a way to rip apart their mentality when he's on the big stage.
He wins that $100,000 check every time. Yeah, and we all going to have the two players come on to
the main stage in a couple of seconds. SOS has a lot of fun girls. They've been screaming. We've been
hearing them. They were coming through the microphones coming through and there's quite a few of them.
They got all their signs up. Hopefully, Bionna can overpower the fun girls, but Bionna has a lot of
momentum behind him. James, he's got the community backing. He's feeling good. He's happy up on stage.
Yeah. He feels like he can win this. It looks to me as when we were sat at the
Caster's desk and you guys were interviewing that he seemed quite relaxed. I mean, I don't know if
you guys got that feel from him, but he, and that is actually kind of rare to see for like a
Korean just kind of having a very kind of chirpy and smiley attitude towards this kind of situation.
Likewise, though on the other side, SOS is normally always like that when I really look at him.
So it's quite the clash to be honest.
Bionna realizes here what's happening. He's on top of his game. He's playing really well and he knows
that girls all boys, there are going to be a lot of fans here for him if he were to win this
regardless. Yeah, it's almost like a dream come true isn't it, because he came into the tournament
and was like, what are we going to be playing in this tournament? And then he went through the quarter
finals. He's gone through the semis and to win this as well on top, it would just all make sense
together. What do you think James? I mean, I would. I mean, him being this weird enigma for so long
that everyone was hyping up but kind of jokingly and just can, yeah, I've only kissed for jail,
but then he comes back and he's actually really good. I don't know what to say. It's a bizarre
weird twist that he's actually come and been this great. Yeah, I mean, but how many times do fairy
tales come true? Sure, I'll finish that there, but not for him. I think there are a lot more
people on Reddit right now cheering for him. So he's got that wave of momentum man. And let's face
it, StarCraft Reddit is where champions are truly made. Absolutely. But realistically, there's obviously,
you know, it's not, it's not $100,000 first place here, but it is still a chunk of money. It's 12,000
for first place, which SOS obviously pennies for him. But as he said when he was up here, when he
gets to a final, he does do well on them and he rarely, rarely loses when he gets to a grand final.
That's what that mentality's got a confidence. Absolutely. That's true, but at the same time,
there are a lot of indicators that might point out that it's going to be a tough game for him.
Yeah. First, the fact that they played in the SSL qualifiers not too long ago in which Bjorn was
able to stop SOS to run very early, like in the very qualifier for the tournament. It's like, what's
SOS supposed to be in this tournament? And Bjorn stopped him with a 2-0. So also, I think Bjorn is,
he's been really impressive against Protoss. He has played almost 50 series in Legacy of the Voids,
recorded and posted on Lady Gulag against Protoss and he's 180% of them. SOS only three series
on Legacy of the Void and he's only one of them and one of those losses, one of those two losses
was against Bjorn. So if you look at that, you have to be telling yourself this could be
really tough here for SOS to win this. Oh, there is Bjorn and there's the Fangirl screaming for us.
It's a T-Jack lap. And of course they're playing for the trophy in the middle of the stage.
And it is going to be a best of seven. Every single map is going to be played two smiles from both.
Good to see. Bjorn's a happy man right now. He's been waiting for this man. This is the moment.
He's having a grand finals. He's having a grand finals. He's about to play a couple,
a couple liberators in some mineral lines. Of course he's smiling.
We talked to it very little bit with SOS about the recent balance change.
They mostly changes this match up to any of the others. What are your thoughts here, Todd,
in the adept change in how that could affect SOS? It only was implemented a couple of days ago.
Not much time to really start to innovate and change around the match up, what he's practiced.
Really not a lot of time. And to be honest though, at the same time I feel like this guy
is considered a genius. So it doesn't really strike me as the type of
protost that needs to play, you know, what are present at the adept all in every single game to be
successful. But the fact that adepts have been changed in the way they've been,
definitely going to make it harder for you to be able to do better here.
And honestly, Bjorn, with the way he's been playing so far in this tournament and the way he
looks very confident, I don't even seem stopping with the aggression here just because he's playing
SOS. I just seem like opening regular, you know, commence center into widow mine drop into liberator,
skilling probes, getting some tanks back at home because he loves to do that to be safe against
blink stalker so he can have ground army and just playing solid all around good terrain versus
protost together. I think it's a great way as well. I mean, against SOS. SOS normally
thrives when he is the one dictating the pace of the game. But if Bjorn concedes that away from
him early on and be like the aggressor early on trying to put on some harassment, I think that'd
be a great way for him to win. Yeah, you agree with that, that pick? Yeah, I mean, when it comes
down to it, SOS thrives when he's the one dictating the pace. He's not a guy who sits back and
thinks he's just going to win in the late game. He's going to find edges and he's going to work as
hard as he can to get that momentum going. I think we're going to see Dark Templar at least one game,
probably two or three. I think we're going to see a lot of aggression out of him, but not necessarily
the adaptor whopperism stuff, which has been so famous in recent weeks. All right, then it's time
for the all famous predictions. Clarice, you're on the end, so I have to ask you. I've got to go
with the community from large, I guess. I've got to go with Bjorn, and I'm going to go for
four two in the end, that you and the Twitch chat are together right now. Not quite as much as
Nathanius, but not as much as Nathanius. Nathanius is melded with them, which Todd.
It absolutely paints me to agree with Kaelar, but I'm not going to go with John as well, and a cheeky
fall three. You guys are whole thing. That's a joke, but I was going to go for Bjorn as well, but I'm
going for two, but I'm going to actually say, you know, this is going to be some momentum based,
there's so much on the line. I think SOS is going to keep it together better. He's going to get
under Bjorn's skin here. So I'm going to say a four two to SOS, actually. All right, well, thank you
very much, Pete. Thank you very much, Todd and Kaelar is for your predictions. It is now time to
begin the grand finals of the entire stream masters here in Taipei. One of these two players is going
home with the trophy, going home with $12,000. The other player is unfortunately just a mere second
place finisher. Let's head over to the commentary team for this one. Of course, it's Kaelar is in Todd.
It is time for the grand finals here of the until extreme masters Taipei hype a bound here as we
are going to be starting things off on ruins of Sarah's here in this best of seven between SOS and
Bjorn, a two time bliss con world champion and a one time in telextreme masters world champion
goes up against the guy who has accomplished almost nothing in his career, but is here in the
grand final after doing so well at the start, like you see the void. Bjorn is a lifetime badass,
but he definitely needs to prove something here. Can he win this tournament? It's going to take some
really good games to for him to win the best of seven against SOS for sure. Yes, it is. All right,
so as we get into this, I believe I may have to change something here on my PC a moment.
Yes, John looking intense here as we're about to get into map number one on ruins of Sarah's
a little bit of the the mouth open actually. Stowing down you a little bit as SOS also looking
tense here in the starts. All right, and we are back and good to go. So up to the top left as well,
we have our pollu protest. It is Jinag Greenwings SOS. Going for Nexus first in map number one. What else?
All right, so what a way to open up here as we do have the Nexus first. I'm going to be going down here
for SOS Bjorn, is he likely to go for some crazy aggression here? Is he likely to try and do so?
I mean cross-maps on ruins, sorry, it's one of the furthest bonding positions you can have in
the entire map pool right now. I don't know if I would describe it as crazy aggression as long as
he doesn't go all out and like stay on one base, which I think is very unlikely on a map like this
and in map number one. I've seen him go you know for double gas and stuff but like in this game he's
just going to be the standard quick reactor into command center and then down the line he loves to
rush for that stop-orts and mixing different units to try and do some economic harassment. Sometimes
aliens we don't mind anything that he can get his hands on. Liberators are going to be used a lot
of the time actually not just against proto sometimes against Sarah. Quite quite a bit of the
camps that we've seen him against Sarah as well. He's used Liberator so well. I feel like
he's almost got here with his usage of Liberators. He has true understanding on where and when to use him
and he's definitely proven that he's been watching nothing. He has his stream because he uses his
uses them almost as well as Nate does. Almost almost. I mean Nate again, with the twitch chat, one with the
meme machine. He gets so much done with them. So much done. But for now, where is he? Get out.
Okay, what do you see? Saw the reactor. That's all right. I think SOS knows exactly what is
easier from there. He knows that there is a factory behind this, that there's going to be a stop-orts,
some potential Widow Mine drop down the line and actually SOS going for the double gateway here.
He might just be going for a double adept here for some sort of attack behind this. You don't have
to get mothership called that quick versus there. And if you don't know for a fact that they're
attacking so he's keeping on that for now. It's actually going to be a double stalker here instead of
double adept. So maybe a little bit more defensive build here. What else does he get to? There it is,
the Twilight's Council. I thought it might be a Stargate but with how Delaydy would have been here.
The thing is with the adept being how they are now. I mean we've seen a lot of proto as well
kind of go over to Walls Blinkstalkers right and use those to great effects for like even just kind
of holding off against initial aggression and then putting on some pressure later on. Yeah. I mean
I don't think it's like adept's not bad or anything now. Not that's good as they used to be. They
are not ridiculous anymore. Let's just put it that way. But they can still do stuff, you know,
especially with resonating glaves. Yeah. Still quite strong. Let's see if you're ready for Bjorn.
Is moving over to the left side. Quite aggressively here to try and keep an eye on things. I
suppose controlling this watch tower. I thought he was going to stick around and like
controlling just in case it was a wall. I think this is going to be a quick third for us. Look at this.
He's only on two gateways, gets the Robo folks. He started Blink already and he's going to be a
quick third next this year. And he is covering all of these bases with stalkers and trying to prevent
a scout. So now Bjorn is going to be misled. He's caused the third base there. He's no third
starting. Scan's the main. He's just a Robo double gates and something being researched right now
in the twilight council. This could be anything. This could be adept with additional gateways
on the natural. Yeah. Yeah. I don't think that out of four things he can somehow expect that there
is a third base on the way and this could be really good if I so as because his economy is going
to completely take off. He's going to have Blink stalkers or just stalkers in general to deal with
the liberators that are going to hit him and he's going to have enough. I think to defend against
those windomines. Yeah, I should do. The thing is is that at least the windomines from this
direction will spot out the third base one more dimension unless it changes some calls drastically.
Actually wait the timing on that mothership point looks like it's it's going to align up very well
with when the Medivac gets there I think. Yeah it's going all the way around. He's going to
spot that base. He's not going to spot the third. Oh my yeah. The mothership call. He said it
towards the natural. Look at the timing on the mothership point. It's literally going to get there
as the Medivac arrives. That's so sick. So he sees the third. He sees double fours as well as he
flies on into this with a to this with a mind drop and burrowing. He even kills one of the phone
over charge. I mean yeah one probe is going to die but who cares behind his observer is going to
come there. D-Mine SOS is now going to be saturated on three bases even before Bjorn just he just
started Sturdy CC. Exactly. And Bjorn is so funny because like he almost always does this behind
where he gets like some tanks to make sure he's safe back at home and I think SOS knew that so he's
like you know what I'm going to do. You're going to stay at home. Stay at home. I'm already on three
bases. Double fours gateway explosions going to happen down the line and SOS's production is going
to blow up. He's going to get so many units. Liberators on the way on the left hand side going to
cross over with this Medivac and that'll go home to try and shut the some more units forward
again later on. And this Liberator looking at the positioning of the pylons as well as the
stalkers. I don't think it's going to get more stone here. It's going to be very difficult to find
that sweet spot. And it definitely didn't find it. Just one stalker but I mean I think SOS has
lost one probe and one stalker so far this guy. Yeah, something like that. That's really good.
Well, it's not going well. For Bjorn let's just say that here. 63 workers to 44 RcVs. I mean yes
of course they have mules and eventually that third base will be open running but it's going to take
a while for Bjorn. It's only just started for this. Oh my SOS started for this.
Even before Bjorn has flown his third CC on location. It's like the tempo of the game from either
side it's just completely different. Like the turn of it all is literally only starting now. SOS
just is going to snowball out of control here on everything. Production. He's starting to proxy
some planets on the map. He's going to have so much vision. What is him headed throughout the
main and Dark Shrine. I mean about halfway through done here as one one's about to finish.
Realistically if you're looking at this and thinking well you know Bjorn why didn't he pull
out more aggression again. It's ruins of service. It's so difficult to get over the other side of
the map. These are the best possible spawns for SOS to execute this vastly greedy style that he
is exuding here. Let me reformulate what you just said. Realistically Bjorn is in a lot of trouble
if not dead. Yes. I guess he's going to be really talk for him to somehow make something happen
in this game even though like right now supply wise there is not a huge gap. SOS is to be careful
though. If he messes up like if he loses his war prism recklessly here it could be in big trouble.
If he doesn't realize there is drops headed across the map here also could this could mean big trouble
but with the amount of gateways that he has I really can't imagine SOS somehow messing up big
and off here for him to be throwing away this game. It's six gateways. He definitely needs more by
the way I think like 10 12 would be really nice. And actually walked in some more at that
stone towards the bottom where he's like even just walked up the mountain then substituted
them for dark templars that he's going to send on in a moment. So this is really quite scary
here for Bjorn. Like the ramp up in how much supply SOS is going to have soon is going to be huge
but he doesn't really have much to defend this location right now. Where's the mother ship
car? I'm not even sure. I'm really surprised that Bjorn actually didn't detect the base here
because he was pretty exposed but he's still laying that here for now. Dark Templar is in the
mix of all of this. He actually spots it before it even gets a siphon and that will be one dark
templar already going down but there's still two in this warp rhythm. Little bit surprised that
charge hasn't started yet but maybe SOS wants to stay on adept stalkers going in for kill on
this some of these units they instantly die as soon as they get warped in. That's a great move
here. Why Bjorn's trying to start equalizing things? He's like he realizes he has to get out of
there that's a huge army. High templars were just a little bit too far here to feed back on time.
DT is going to do some damage. He can even pick up behind his oh he gets a missile turret with the
two DTs. That's each time a strand of help out through upstound the scan but instantly gets
picked up at SOS. Wow what a start of this game. Behind is he's going to be adding on even more
gateways. His production is just going to be so insane. He's on 71 probes. Is that not a little
excessive? I mean I think it's a great economy but yeah I think he's the perfect number but he
definitely needs to make sure he has the production facilities here to to spend all of his minerals.
Yeah. Yeah. So a couple more gateways would be nice maybe even a second robo, some kind of robo
but I mean two two finishes now like Bjorn doing so much trouble mate. He starts his own two
two and he's keeping up his supply but I don't see these attacks doing enough. He'll be like
he's definitely got some initiative here to try and make something happen. He's done a really
good job to actually keep up in terms of macro. He's got quite a strong army himself. Storm finished.
That's the big problem here. That is true and three three is already on the way before two two is
even halfway complete. So Bjorn has to again he basically has to drive his opponents crazy with
these drops. But SOS knows I think that this is one of the only ways he can lose this game so he's
left some Templar here at this 12 o'clock base and he's getting extra cannons there.
Make sure he can defend with just that and he's actually throwing down cannons in his main base as
well. No he knows yet though on that Templar. If Bjorn was to hit that position right now and he
snipe that would be great I think for him. Because it's got to be on the way. Spots the
army in the middle of the map here and drops the scan realizing the high templates are with it
and knows now that Storm is very much so available to him. I'm gonna try and go in here. Storm
pressuring that back allowing him for the warp him even if that pilot goes down at the front
there's still one to back it up so there's the depth will not get cancelled.
Bjorn was very impressive actually earlier against Salky with the ghosts like his control was
I thought really really good but it's very different against Rotos. He's such a different story.
When you have so many high templates already placed down on the map there's no room for mistake
here for a turn. SOS gonna start a fifth base. I mean why not like he's so rich already.
It's crazy as I said you know to begin with it feels like the tempo is just off.
Whoa! For Bjorn in comparison. Stargate starts.
Ooh. So maybe like an Oracle first to make sure he can reveal the entire
Tianan army to take a good engagement or even like use his item plush to snipe stuff.
I'm not sure what these units were doing there maybe he wanted to set them up on the right
hand side to counter attack when Bjorn was gonna move out but that's gonna be taken out now
and people are actually ahead in supply right now. They're going down a lot of
the depth field walked in into the main base also a few more gonna follow that up
also already shading forwards and looking to get onto what feels.
Oh, Stargate is gonna go down and SOS wants to go for Tempest. I think you realize that once you
have high 10 plus you force ghost out of your opponent when he's great against ghost but bunch of
Tempest. Yeah that's true. It's gonna be difficult for him to really deal with flea
beacons on the way as well these adaptors are still doing big big dab. This is what's the main.
This is even just too by time like this is not even supposed to do that much damage but right now
his tail has gone quite a bit. It's so many adepts. I mean I can't see some Marines it's so many
adept they're not exactly getting you know full combat efficiency off compared to the previous
patch that they were on but still this is very very powerful here. Fy SOS is gonna greet this
with ease by the looks of things. There are not any high templates there for the storm but they're
coming in from the back here and they're gonna lay down the storms on towards some of this bio
they sacrifice themselves but they push it all the way back. Yeah the observer was sniped though
but these units in the main are already doing so much damage for SOS and he's got such an
insane economy that he can just keep on warping there. Yeah. Bjorn struggling to even stay here
in his main base and somehow defend that position in the meantime. Tempest production is not
gonna start though. Bjorn never got to a 4th. Never mind of the 5th that is going up for SOS
behind this so you're totally on the money when you say the economy advantages so much here for SOS
he is now burning down even just a few more of these units anything that dies is fantastic
as well as is on the march towards the opponent's main. I think he realizes that even like this army
to be honest is expandable with the income that he has with the Tempest is getting now being
saturated on five bases against the ten that just lost this many SIVs he's gonna mean so much
trouble here for Bjorn. He's not even mining from his main he's 36 SIVs to 72 probes the income
is basically double here for a SOS. We already knew he was reaching real life apparently he's in the
game about as equally. Yeah this is ridiculous I mean that warpers and yes goes down up towards
the top but at the same time the bio army here isn't gonna have the easiest time but it's
to be in place. There's so much energy that's four storms you're available.
Hmm. Well, guess pushed away but the third base has had to be forced to lift up. He dropped
scans in the main because he was being harassed by some dark temp lars cancelling add-ons and not
for a moment and I guess he started the wrong ones that I wanted. Wow Bjorn. He's keeping up
in supply nicely but I mean he's just like at the basic bio force that you go for a steering
in terms of ghosts he's got zero I feel like Bjorn's gonna move across the map get shot at by the
Tempest type gg and leave. Yeah that's there's nothing he can do against it literally nothing right
now. I can attempt to stem up some of his Marines and hope that they've died but in the first
time. Yeah. He's just a big round army doesn't wreck him. Oh clear evaporated and even plus one
air weapons going for these Tempest. This is SOS he's that confident that he's actually flying
across the map right now. Oh why not. He's at home he's making himself at home. Yeah.
He's especially in the booth just putting his feet up getting relaxed getting calm
taking a crushing victory over Bjorn here it would really really hurt but again runes of
Seraph's on cross spawns it is difficult here for Bjorn we can see that very clearly and
their depths once again I'm just causing disruption in the main SOS does not care about no patch man.
Nope not at all six base still no potential harass here for Bjorn. Just keep sending
spawns. Oh cool. So rotating he revelates this army and then all the video minds are
revision and oh this is yeah there's nothing actually I think that Bjorn can do here he wouldn't
need like an insane amount of Vikings to even have a chance but there's high 10 plus anyway so
I think he even spotted those liberators trying to go on the offensive down towards the bottom
but fourth base is trying to erect and it will not happen probably. What presuming the main?
It's the war present. He's killed that. No you're made one but actually you had never
Oh well. Carious he's starting to carry us. Oh my he's having fun now. Yeah I think so yeah
it reminds me of that altitude game back in Katowice. Yeah three carriers on the way.
I think it was against Jack G back then. I mean to be fair if you can get enough carriers out
then they're amazing but the oftentimes you just never have a window to actually get to them.
Where are you going Bjorn? Your army is revealed bro. You think you're gonna escape?
It's the weirdest. It's the weirdest game of Katowice. You can't escape me.
Actually he's separated off a bit of his army here so this is actually quite clever by Bjorn.
He's gonna take the straight-up engage in towards the top. Yeah the high 10 plaza I think got the
MP on time here for them once to really do much and on the left hand side he's actually not
doing too bad. The war pin's gonna go down here Bjorn trying to keep himself in this.
Gigi is being wiped in here to try and take out as much value as possible before scan his youth
but Bjorn with the eagle eye once again uses that perfectly on time. He goes that off and now he's
just abusing the immobility of this army. He's gonna hit the north, swear he's hitting the west here.
Oh hitting the north and the west that is one of the most powerful little plays you can do here
as Bjorn considering again the immobility of these tempis. It's very very difficult the next
is gonna end up falling. I don't have to keep in it. How many carriers are we at though?
Let's do clean teeth with that high template here. Get off my lawn man. Get off here.
Nice up there. Chased everything away with one single storm. Carriers is gonna be the, I feel the
cherry on top of the cake here for SOS. I'm plus two weapons going down for that as well. Oh,
oh this is interesting in the middle of the map I didn't notice this for a moment. Yeah.
It's a good setup here to cover the tempis and also the high temp lary against the ghost in
particular. This is actually gonna be the golden armata like we end up having a look.
Actually, Bjorn might go into a base straight here. Realizing if you can't win the fights
then you shouldn't take a fight. That's a very important rule of StarCraft. So I think if you realize
that if you realize this that there is this many carriers and you can't win the fight
you should just try to stay out on the map and counterattack anytime that SOS moves out.
Yeah, it makes a lot of sense. It's one of the only ways really. He's gonna have to be
well dealing with this army is not on suicide. I don't mind anything else. A couple of
that were sent into a base here but didn't really do much. Kaira is having spotted. So now this is
the time for Bjorn to realize that this game is not going his way and he's probably not gonna win any fights
ever. Exactly. Golden. Golden bases being taken on ruins of Saras and I mean with these cannon
positions he has a high ground, a high temp plus that have full energy carriers and tempis.
This isn't gonna get broken. Both like trying to win a fight is gonna be hard but trying to
base straight against the protos that's on this many bases with high temp plus everywhere and with
cannon positions equally gonna be as hard. So I think Bjorn might be planning on, he's making a
lot of marines. He might be planning on EMP everything killing all the interceptors and winning the
fight this way. Maybe the kairas do are gonna have so much damage outputs if SOS is able to get a few
more right now. It's just the six ones. So in terms of interceptors it's not gonna be necessarily
that super overwhelming force. So I guess he's mostly gonna rely on the MPs here to try and win this
if he can hit all the item plus. I still really like what he's doing with these small chunks of
units just hitting, hitting wherever he can. It's very important that he keeps his opponent on his
toes, keeps him moving, make sure that he's not gonna get attacked through the middle. I mean remember
innovation versus SOS back when in the world finals that took place in Korea. I think it was
new planet S where SOS tried to go for tempest and innovation just attacked all over the place. SOS
had no mobility on one of the smallest maps that you can think of and somehow innovation was
able to kill him quite easily by just taking out units, bases, all over the place with the mobility
that he has and I think that's what Jong is trying to do here but not in the same way like he's
more trying to buy time here for him to keep on expanding and staying alive in this game.
And dark handplasers gonna cut off a few ghosts here which is actually not too bad all.
Is that very stodo? That's the thing they get chased on ghosts. Unlike the rest of the army that
can steam and run away. Yeah he's gonna run away so badly. Every single fight that comes along
and another poke up the wall to top but the defense is still there for SOS who is just trying to
wear him down slowly. Another big drop down towards the bottom left maybe and do something.
Man what a tournament and what a bunch of games here we see the two semis where insane and now
first game in this best of seven grand finals, Kairos and tempest. I mean SOS was on full
bases that the 730 mark and now he's on his seventh down towards the middle. He's just
doing a lot of damage here and really worth this for that left hand side army here for him.
Because there's a couple high ten plush nearby that has so much energy.
Meri, they are right down the right. I'll find the high back. He did that even could do a lot there.
He wanted to drop some of those Marines up on the high ground but it didn't manage to actually get
that up there at all. At the same time big big damage going down here from the Kairos and tempest.
It's gonna have to be a full blown base straight here for FBUN. He cannot take that directly
on in the middle of this map. It doesn't have nearly as much firepower as he's opponent though.
It's 134 and he's supplied to 113 right now and the production of Vion is gonna be shut down
pretty much instantly here while this hits. Does he have an observer with his arm?
He's got a couple out on the map. There's some widow mines.
He's trying to get storms off on any other spy that he can but as he's doing all of his
infrastructure is being torn apart. I mean on paper this is not really a winner for Vion and his
army is being defended here on the left hand side. There's no way it's gonna take out this
tempest or carriers anytime soon. It's not like you can even play forward draw here.
No. The theory is actually Kairos and tempest. Yeah, the buildings by way.
Vion trying is very very best here in the past like even like 10 minutes.
13 minutes also. Look at these guys down there.
Well there you go. GG.
Double prints and one goes running to the tempest and wasn't enough.
What a ridiculous start there from SOS. I mean he got the best of everything really.
He got the dream of he was able to easily expand his opponent out maneuver his opponent.
You know exactly how to develop a lead into a bigger lead.
Yeah. Yes. It's not a bad start.
It's not a bad start. How good is with this stuff?
Like gets a good opponent and then from there it really seems like you just can't recover.
Really? There's not much to do.
That was very very tough on Vion there indeed. Just how is this gonna be our next map?
I really, you know, we have to go back to cross spawns rooms of Seris.
It is difficult for him to get over there and be aggressive. At least some of these smaller
or at least closer spawning position maps will allow him to have a bit more leverage over his
opponent in the other game because SOS exploited him to a tee there.
An absolute tee. I mean he didn't even know where the spawning positions were before he was
going for that next one very early on and then into the well he didn't know for the third but
actually even going back to that quick third base even before that he was a nexus first.
SOS like it seems like especially like you think that we see style and being able to throw
in crazy builds it'd be good in best of one and he is but in best of seven he changes builds
every single game from map to map always picks something that's really good very rarely gets it wrong.
It's so crazy. Yes it even had that much time to think about this like it literally like
just played this match just finished against hero and now he's starting his run.
All right well we're getting into it. If SOS takes the second game I may have to change my prediction
because this is just that was too fierce as we have spawning up to the top right it will be our
red terror representing X-Team it is beyond and I would be so you jumping shape at the first
time of hardship. Hey man if I I will admit when I'm wrong for sure like if SOS is able to pull
this one out of the bag as well and then down to the bottom left thank corner we have our blue
pro toss it's Gen Agree Mings SOS actually he's down in the bottom left but he's already sending
a probe across the map. Yes what is this for? This might just be like a really quick scout to make
sure he doesn't get walled out maybe maybe maybe he was afraid of some kind of two rags you know
like these players the thing about these two is that I'm pretty sure you know they practice a lot
on the ladder in particular beyond and I feel like if they've met recently and SOS would have
gone on two rags on this map after a map number one like this it's perfectly fine to say well you
know what I might be starting to destroy him already mentally in his best of seven from map number
one so I'm gonna be extra safe and scout really really quickly to see exactly what is going for.
SOS has put a little bit of pressure on against that SCV not too much beyond reveals that easily.
Next is going to go down behind this for SOS so really just ramping up the ramping up the economy
in the end and if he gets himself in a in a great economic position before not necessarily as
ridiculous as the last what type game but he can still find himself in a good probe advantage as
long as the Crudebrew stays on these Nexus. Yeah and I mean from Jon as well like somebody
scouts who this fast like this isn't an unusual timing. Jon didn't even go for a scout himself but
it's probably yeah maybe getting a little bit paranoid especially because he's playing SOS like
this could mean a number of things but so far he's not necessarily overreacting or if or anything
and he's just gonna be going for the factory here behind this. All right so command center finishing
up soon and SOS talking with thinking stock it yeah target's gonna be the way.
So with the positioning behind the mineral lines usual there is a number of ways you can use
a stock it here and one of the more popular ones is actually there is two main ones I feel
personally you either get an Oracle and then you go for a quick third which against any kind of push
like it can be difficult if there is like a bunch of Marines and a cyclone attacking you or
pressuring you especially if the chance getting turrets behind this knowing that there could be
some kind of target play with new thermal being very successful with this kind of build or you can
just play Finix's. Finix's are super good like overall they are a very well-rounded unit that can
pick up Widow mines which guess what Jon loves to get almost every single game he always goes for that
factory always goes for that stop-ort as well and drops a bunch of Widow mines but in this case he's
gonna be the Oracle with the quick third base here for SOS. All right well you're not near the side
as I say with that stargate star port going down even I should say Widow mines being add to
them maybe a little bit of a meta backdrop in but alternatively you could use them Widow
mine defensively set it up behind a sort of like a refinery or something like that. I don't think
his SOS is never gonna flange Oracle into a Widow mine defensive Widow mine that's just not gonna happen
is that those beyond scan domain of SOS I don't think he's going to with these next scan that
will come up in domain so far he's exactly nothing didn't even bother send that on SV to try and
see what SOS was up to so he needs some intel but as soon as he sees the Oracle I guess that does give
him a little bit anyway he's gonna relocate the Widow mine I don't think the Oracle's gonna fly
into that it's going towards the back mineral line there SOS by the way this time around didn't
delay the modorship course so it's gonna have quite a bit of energy here down the line to really help
with the defense oh my chase out that way oh very close yeah I think he spotted it yeah no what wow
it attracts for just a second split second that was not supposed to happen no I told you that
an Oracle of SOS will not fly into a Widow mine guess what I was wrong myself and I admit it
and in this case actually it's pretty bad that Oracle is supposed to be a massive threat is supposed
to even if he doesn't do any damage to consistently reveal the tyrann army and behind this
SOS is even very hesitant here I think for a second okay he restarts the second Phoenix
and it looks like he just wants to play with Phoenixes and adepts on the ground which is a good style
but if the tyrann was to play with mass marines and tanks and those a big push with Medivacs
marines and tanks it's so hard to deal with this I think with my crows oh this is one of
the adepts that he's gonna lose some uh for sure I guess there's some out of marines here beyond
really taking advantage of his position at the moment bringing back the Phoenixes well to
cross fresh against the Medivacs but there's not that many adepts really here to help out against
this it's such a powerful little pull you're doing this many pro by so important you kill eight so
now the Walker counties even but we've got a turn we said 30s here about to finish nine worker
kills in total really good stuff here for beyond really taking advantage of what you could do I mean
as you said that Oracle is normally supposed to keep those marines back at home being a threat but
with it dying off as quickly as it did or even defense like be there and defend but not flying
to a widow man and die this is a very characteristic mistake here that we saw out of SOS and he
definitely paid the price for it behind this and now we've got beyond going into uh lots of bio he
just made one single tank I really feel like if you don't have gone for like a lot of tanks and marines
this style can be very effective against what we see SOS doing but since SOS had such an earlier
third then uh then most of the time maybe we'll have been risky it would have been an all in clearly
so in this case bjone is just gonna try to play pretty solid double upgrade from the ebay
and the third base in mobile um shade's gonna head on forwards I will look around do it I dare you
that's what bjone is saying right now and he said he's like no no no no no no no SOS I maybe this crazy
but I'm not that crazy um third base is about to finish up temporal archives going down as well
double upgrades could start pretty soon he does have the gaps available for them uh and getting
a little bit of a catch up on towards the one one it's already started for bjone would be nice
already for being on five racks here by the way for a bjone means that his production
from this point onwards he's gonna really really take off
it's like he's always supposed to be ahead in army supply here at this point in the game but
from the moment you start having like say arounds even just too many vaks to be honest I was gonna say
four but he might even try and add some liberators here earlier no case start some medieval 3 and 4
yet so four medievals is really that number where when you have an army this big year as tian you have a
lot of room to try and drop and do some damage especially not at overcharge he's a lot more costy
don't get canceled because he saw that the tyrann army here was out of position so that's
gonna do a little bit of damage and by some time and he's gonna get out behind this yeah very very
nicely done overall it doesn't leave any units to actually greet that down towards the bottom
and bye bye one adept good guys for four workers in total so you don't think about it all
more gateways gonna go down here as s os gets a bunch of cannons in his mains goes for storm
it's interesting actually not to see charge you know in uh in much more sort of like a roti-esque style
where you get charge high temp bars and usually opening with blinks stalkers like in this case here
it seems like s os prefers to go stalker adept heavy skip an italian zealots and then they
get 10 get to a bunch of high temp bars yes boss fields available didn't actually even use them
guardians shield was the attempt that in storms will buy the time prep a pit of seal the man with
boss fields that could have been a few extra kills that but it would have picked up with the meta
vans it's really cool actually to see beyond like place so well in game number two and starting is
two two before his opponents one one even finished year a second ago so he's ahead on upgrades
and then from there i feel like he's just he doesn't even have to play aggressive anymore really
i mean if you work to row into 87 armies of like this is 44 right now he's gonna get high
temp bar forward there and actually that alleviates all of the storm potential he could actually rip
this army apart if he's not careful the arcongas focus down those attempts do not have the firepower
here to deal with this and another high temp bar comes in it has one storm available look at the
reinforcement coming in from beyond here this is a huge army has available there's one storm
to split up and just actually maneuver around this there is no more gateway units here left
and the other charges used to late yeah way too late that pilot was almost dead anyway and that's
gonna be a nexus gone this is a great little move here but beyond he was able to deal with the
aggression there's gonna be the warp of the depths towards the back here but this is desperation times
for s os where the nexus are going down and all of these are dead being cleaned up beyond is really
in the driving seat right now and he sensed it he i mean he sensed all out of the front gg and he
will pile the series there so a bit more opportunity for him to be aggressive really pays off
that's what i'm talking about man that's the beyond we all know and love we all knew he's capable
of doing this sure in map number one s os open with a nice surprising nexus first and snowball
out of control from there but in map number two young proves that he can go head to head to to to
with this guy here that destroyed him in map number one with temp as encounters and he did it in
very convincing fashion yeah made a lot of bio attack properly sure losing the oracle helped a lot
for bion but in this case it was s os is mistaken even if the oracle had been alive he wouldn't
necessarily have changed that much he made a lot of units and attacked properly at the exact
right timing he needed to go for to win the game here and i imagine he's anticipating more maps where
he can put himself in a more aggressive stance pre-interests this is going to be our next map
here between these two and we are almost ready to get in s os is not going to get himself that
to all lead early on in this series so i am not changing my prediction just yet but
gotta give credit where credits us so i still looks good so looks good i can't believe actually
that he flew an oracle into a with a mind like this this is very uncharacteristic i feel like he
only did it because i said it to spite you but the thing is that the oracle was locked on for a
brief moment so if he was actually paying attention he would have known that with a mind was there but
i guess he was doing something else i honestly this is not supposed to happen especially like
i mentioned john does disomers every game if not every game he gets rid of my cinematic back why would
you find his base like this all right getting into a game at number three so we have spawning up
to the top left hand corner representing x team tying up the series it is beyond
all right for himself if you let his macro go wild then wow wow wow macro go wild
and down to the bottom right hand corner we have our blue protest representing jinn air green wings
it is s os s so as you put him on a map like this with a couple gold bases man you're gonna
you're in for a treat definitely care bubble up throwing in something crazy so we'll see
already had some cool game already on this map i can see you know but now going up against the
tyran i feel like he honestly doesn't have to get too fancy anymore because if he gets caught
of god if he somehow gets scouted it's gonna be really bad for him so s os sometimes the
surprising thing for a player like s os is gonna be to just play purely standard if you were to do
something like this then whereas like john would be scouting all over the place to try and make
sure he's not getting surprised and it could be a good thing but guess what s os is just gonna be s os
to what he does best which is yeah be himself in the omeland of the has over here in tywan
oh yes he takes a gold base very quickly
has to recently qualify in the WCS challenge match for karevits he might not be in the audience
he's like hey that's my build he's like he's like showing copy cards but s os is a two time world
champion house and he's like oh all right so what this is my homeland in my build because of the ramp
has a little poke round as well not too much so you can really get done here although
but this gold base once again i mean there's a pilot going down in a very stargate s position
once again for s os he might try it and he might look to do some damage usually with this
kind of build though it's probably better to just go twilight i think personally
mm-hmm are you eager to cast has again in the future by the way always always i mean
has plus legacy the void can only mean great things right so hey no twilight yet and s os is going
high on gas here so maybe you're right can we see your cheeky stargates as the first adaptor
is about to finish it's like i won't make the same mistake because i did last game
back potentially come true i like how small the choice though still a twilight yeah it's in the
place i mentioned but this is century why would you get a century usually you never get a century
here with adebs being as good as they are are you ready for the hallucinated oracle
into noracle into that that was not the plan guys whoa that's a quick forge
much quicker than i was expecting really wants to get those upgrades going considering the position
he was in the last game one very important thing to take in consideration here is that because
he opened with the gold first the income of s os is going to be much greater than usual so usually
you can do some adjustments to your build he might just be saying here with this i want to go into
a lot of gateway units beats charge lots or adebs with resonating laves so a lot of gateway but no
another gold base starts oh my god i told you from the start that on my place so i'm s os
he's seeing crazy things so i guess the forge he's to have that potential for detection with
some cannons because we don't mind we don't mind drops there can be very very scary in this situation
like i mean there will not be any any robo and observers and behind this he's going to drop down
a bunch of gateways imagine s os goes like if ten gateways and makes ten trillion stalkers here
and goes across the map and keeps on bleaking if Bjorn was doing some early game scouting against s os
then s os with zero units ever in these early minutes would just be like plundered but this is
this is ridiculous Bjorn just scanned the main actually off s os he must be like wait what
there is a spinning forge and two very late gateways being made so early an only arm of grades
actually used to be a staple for a long time how do you see that to the right goal by doing oh so sick
so sick and it does nothing other than have a look around i think it did it didn't cross the path
of this meta back right i mean he's anticipating it anyway so he's going to out on the cannon
towards this location no down i mean the thing is though there is a forge he can just de-mind with
cannons yeah they don't take that long time to make he's 29 seconds so all right he has no arm
i can't wait to finish on time in the main and with overcharge this medieval in his middle
mines could have very quickly here oh he pulls the leaf there's not there's no room for him to do
anything just yet it's gonna stay out and get in that meta back worked on the marines are
just waiting in that position though in emitteratory man behind him next is
he's gonna go for the pylon first open up the make sure the cannon can't do anything
let's see there's guardians here available bring the little mines in lace each to your
location and so he's gonna drop the windomines oh but he needs to re-empower the cannon or sniping
it's sniped the cannon he's gonna go right john finds a hole in the defense of s os here
i know there's been two greedy during all of this gets that pylon down the cannon's gonna fall
as well that's a hallucinated arc on and he actually tanks up another widow mines but not the second
and attempt at a force field that's try seal that in good pick up brings those back
oh nice un-grow here and snipe from john is he gonna be an off though there he's got a few stalkers
s os he's gonna keep on warping in and behind is he's getting more and more gateways here
oh with those stalkers avoiding one of those shots from the widow mine as well he gets himself
the meta back and is able to blink right on past against those marines and liberators flaying
across the map but i think he's been realized how many gateways there is about to be and how many
stalkers there already he wouldn't be throwing away any units he'd be camping back at home trying
to take a third base or doing some kind of two-base all-ins so sick oh wow and this here comes the
liberator now flying on in there is a pylon for the left-hand side that will eventually get
open running to shut this down but some probes will die and you go over charge could take this out
very quickly yeah very quick that's why he's on the sea chicken moving away
jeez so as could have reacted much faster there so maybe getting a little bit stoppy here at this
point but i mean there is weakness on this left-hand side of the goal base on us the stalkers
reposition themselves but there would be very very risky now realize ascent sweetness on the left-hand
side weakness what taught well he's not even like dollar sign or dollar sign is dollar sign gold
brick dollar sign i like how he refuses to take normal bases he's actually skipped his natural
in favor of the middle gold of course he doesn't mind regular minerals unless he's forced to
like in his main he's not a peasants i guess that it also the reasoning of the gold James yay i
guess so the thing is though is that even if he loses a few things here and there he's still making so
much money it's ridiculous at this time around i think i saw as well make sure he doesn't make the same
mistake as in the previous game with not enough production facilities and being caught up god with
an attack he's gonna buy some time here with his adebs actually technically that call to go for
another gold base is wrong because right now john is on two basis and he's gonna go for this
massive timing here yeah it couldn't be a second and i mean he's gonna have so much
the army supplies 74 to 63 the war prisms gonna come back in again and try and buy more time
maybe once the war pin another round if he gets opportunity to actually see really need to keep
that army back it was such a big mistake to sacrifice the liberator i think because he would have
helped so much his army would have done the shit he would have shut down the war prism as well with
it whereas now bjonne is being forced to delay his attack leave some units in his main
whoops thanks for siege tank cast and i'll now they're very very quickly good boost away by bjonne
and he realizes he wants to get as many units as possible here considering there isn't really
splash damage with this protest army the liberator itself is actually gonna fly her back on the way
but there's still that war prism being annoying in the main base more
him i think more than being annoying it's wrecking the end domain yeah it's a fecifizio 10 worker kills
big engagement towards the middle he gets up towards the siege tanks as well brilliant stuff there
there are lots of them are gonna end up falling down seals them off with the force fields in the
arc uh debt are still causing havoc here in the name he has so much money srs has so much money
this is so insane how are you supposed to shut this down as bjonne when there's three gold bases
behind this he can just keep doing this forever yeah he starts on the way he starts the storm
behind this and having snipe 25s sivis here when you have three gold bases i think he's pretty happy
with this creation the income is gonna be ridiculously favoring here s os and oh my god i don't i feel
like the last thing you expect when you go for it two ways like this is to meet you open and somehow
in middle of the map and get shut down yes you're supposed to get in front of this base and then
somehow he barely holds but s os those things is way here it's like not fair i'm watching this game and
it just feels not fair so that's yeah i mean that's that's protests that's that power
our protest oh it's just the power of the gold bases now he's taking them during this game it
suddenly he stings everything into its death he knows he's done haha s os takes the next game
and he puts himself in the lead i like i like the showmanship from bjonne also just keep
suppressing stem bless him and so it's such a beast most protestes choose to complain about
gold bases get us but this one does most most most protestes have the fear of god in them when it
comes to going up against the terrain or whatever i get dropped or whatever i've got we do my
is guessing oh whatever i've got liberators coming along but every single step of the way s os
doesn't care he goes from gold to gold to gold just like his career really
i feel like s os like in in the past lifetime he was like jangyscan or like some six strategists and then
in another lifetime he was also like a zerg player because like he explained it like a zerg here
that guy so fun to watch cannot believe cannot believe he puts himself a game up in this
best of seven at the moment and that was showmanship on both sides but s os who does that who
who has the goal who has the balls only one guy apparently actually maybe has but has would
have lost anyway has in a slightly cheesy way and then like wait a minute this isn't working probably
like two gold bases into like seven gates actually could have pulled it off
all right well we're going to head over to the desk to see what the boys have to think about this
series so far thank you very much calores joined here with pig we've been watching the games and we
do see s os going two games to one now over beyond and an interesting finals to say the least
in a very entertaining one yeah i mean s os and a little protest later saying how are we going to
beat terran now things changed a bit apparently you just get a lot of money and then and then you build
500 times as much stuff as the terran as like s os bringing out the nexus as man this is like some
brood war except he's not playing against mech and the terran's actually trying to attack him but
this is just crazy game i mean what do you think of his overall game plan approaching this i mean
you you impressed with what we're seeing i think it's really cool and i mean he's basically
so far had success in two games with that mass nexus style he's just expanding really fast
and and really staying on that you know that big sort of gateway immortal you've got to you
to kind of use that army for a bit longer right um i think the key weakness that he's found in
beyond's play is the war prism right the war prism is not only buying him a lot of time but
i feel like he's starting out by putting pressure on uh on beyond he's saying i'm expanding so
far so you've got to do something about it and he's always getting the prism over there so fast
anything look i'm just gonna stop you moving out and beyond he's not responding with a viking
or a little pack of marines in the main and that war prism just keeps getting back in over and over
and i feel like s os maybe if he wasn't buying that much time we'd see beyond just push out and be like no
you actually can't take five bases that quickly like bam just slapped down a few bases and win the game
but the war prism is getting it done for him right now so that's just the key there is preventing
this war prism from kind of backstabbing him you'd say yeah definitely think so
all right so i just see you sitting over there with Lil Bo down there did he uh did he have anything
to say i watched in the series i want to shaking his head uh and i love you know he's he's not too
happy with the the state of balance and pv10 honestly he's he's being honestly saying he's just
trying to finance this right now like everything's changed up he can't play the same styles he was
playing before so he's just trying to figure out like what can you do here and uh yeah he basically
said you know beyond needs to push and punish this like s os is just getting so greedy but
if the first push fails and s os holds it it's pretty much game over from there and i mean it
took a long time on serras for s os to close it out but we can see how methodically it was from
that point he's like i got five bases tempers carriers storm everywhere cannons everywhere and it's
like this really really slow patient wave just winning the game so we expecting now from this point
forward i mean we've seen the maps that we played on so far we know the maps that are coming out
are we gonna say a big drastic change now from beyond a lot more aggression
getting into s os's face a lot more how do you say this plan out it's interesting i got to think of
what beyond said in the earlier interview where uh you know i'd been saying he was playing reactively
and he was like no my builds are kind of just working out like it's just kind of lucky i don't think
he's gonna change too much but i definitely think he needs to tweak a few things because so far we've
seen him lose twice too kind of the same strategy obviously one game there were three gold bases which
made it a bit different but he's definitely uh suffering against the war prism harassment and the
mass expand strategy so he's got to he's got to adjust that he's got to block out the war prism and
i think he's in a good spot all right thank you very much baby you're gonna head back to the
commentary team for this one to continue with the grand finals here at the interluxury masters
never thought i'd hear those words of a protoss defeating a turon with a mass expand war prism
strategy but he's right it is working here and now we're gonna go on to orbital shipyard
uh beyond looks the battle back against s os all boys on the desk rest some very good points
pig in particular i do think that's beyond needs to start changing things up a little bit because
right now pion it seemed like he was a puzzle going to the series and he's already been solved
before he even started from s os s os was like you like to make a few units and attack and then get
a third cc i'm just gonna get out of units to defend against what you're gonna throw at me and behind
me some gonna play very greedy build up my economy with very quick bases and crush you with overwhelming
unique production right it is time once again game at number four as we have spawning up to the top
right hand corner are red tarren representing x team it is beyond who has to find a way to shut down
what we're seeing here from s os who spawns down at the bottom left hand corner brody said his name
so let's get it for j agree wins s os s os to men with the belts from this gun spotting it around
his neck like a fighter i just i mean yeah he just raises both belts in the uh on his shoulder man
he is the undisputed champion basically uh two time world champ and then three time if you include
that into extreme as well championship but he was able to win for himself and again with a very
quick scouting on the map where if you wall of you're gonna prevent your opponent not to just go
into your main but also into your natural so s os it seems like in some of the situations he wants to
be able to see exactly what is up against and this time around will be no difference
actually last time he was on dust towers right so i guess both maps where you can wall of
both your base and your natural together he seems like to go for a very quick scout to see what
exactly what is up against i guess i'm gonna start doing that my my as well i won't know
as well i won't know why i'm doing it all right i guess i will know like because s os is doing it but
i mean i'm not necessarily sure that i will know where he achieves it i guess he's just about like
knowing exactly like down to a tee how the opponent's opening yeah yeah gonna ask him i guess
maybe that i'll pound as well you know what happens i guess i think i got it
if you don't scout this early and then you arrive there and the walls are already up you don't know
if it's two bays or one base yeah that's the main thing and if you don't know then you have to
kind of guess and if you get wrong then you lose because if you build up your economy and the
opponent's going one base you won't have enough units to hold and then you die but if you don't
build up your economy and the opponent's has a CC then he's gonna be the one building up his
economy and then you will be in trouble oh that's painful this sv just barely skirts past this
and he already sent a reprieve as well so he was sending this sv out to maybe spot actually he might
proxy a factory now that i look at this oh bum bum bum again that's what's gonna be your robot
bum bum bum okay i'll help just brook lose
well we said he needed to change things up looks like that's what he's doing the funny thing is
is he might still go for widow mines and then just try and drop them in but it's just like closer
so the timings are all a bit wacky this is interesting what is going on
the robo proxy i guess just in a mortal bus like yeah i'm not sure what ss was like exactly
aiming for here maybe i think maybe like immortal production into like bursting down this step all
with a lot of gateways down the line and move up the into the main base with adept's because like
if you take down that wall from taren then the depots not being there you can just send in adept's
and kill your opponent actually he doesn't want to send this reprieve in such a way that it would
lure it back towards these buildings to spot so he's gonna be careful about how he moves with that
it's gonna die warpism is on the way here from ss and at least one more gateway so i guess he's
gonna be some kind of a dead a dead drop here the vision of the automaton 2000 spots that
oh the reaper died i got it finally and bion is not producing anything here with the factory so maybe
okay it was late i don't know why i i feel like a liberator maybe should get a liberator than
maybe instead of medieval ss is back in the driving seat though look at how this is playing out i
feel that yeah okay there'll be window mines and mineral lines and stuff but there may be the
possibility of this actually just crippling damage on that so i suspect as well the fact alone
that bion went for a 30 c instead of additional barracks before yeah and the fact that he doesn't
have his factory back at home he's gonna make it so hard for him to hold this he has a couple marines
to work with here but against so many adept's here that they are gonna be in this base it's gonna
be really hard for him to hold get himself an sdv already showing down income on this location
getting as many sdv as possible the shades go forwards he sees how many marines are there but
there is gonna be other mortal knocking on his door in just a second as long as he couples up with
all the extra units that are gonna warp in and we don't mind in the main boom all right just two probes
in the first place but let's see in detection wise there is no observer being made i think
was that so i see just salining i think i'm just gonna take out the wall like i spoke about earlier
he's gonna supply block actually bion quite heavy there you can get second him all with this the
liberator needs to be out and it needs to get back there fast he actually show up here me well
he's in desperation mode now all the sdv's come off the line here for bion he knows that this is a
bit of a critical position to be in wall prism picks up one of the s stalkers picks up a second one
one in wall for the back here is being a little bit lazy i think bion might just die yeah bion
isn't really mining much i told you while all of this is going on the fact that there is a war
prism he's just gonna lose nothing there he can pick up everything here real sos he keeps on
kiting back the sdv's not even mining anymore sure there is a widow miner cross the map but it's
not killing nearly enough no i picked up all of those units there as well shittles them out and
gets that so far as well great little war prism micro there you really need to kill that war
prism with the liberator there's only two stalkers there maybe you can try and get a few shots
off on it but at the same time it's just gonna try and go for siege up anyway move straight
out of that circle it's not being used at all and bion is taking massive massive damage here sos
kills off the liberator and sos is on the way to cause himself a three one lead here with all
of the marines dying there is nothing left back at home he drops the scan into the natural i've
bit a wall all of this is going on and bion is evacuring he's having none of it
oh dear me sos he is running rampant who stops this guy in championship matches i'm not really
sure but at the moment it's definitely not bion as he's hoping that these widow mines can kill off
26 extra s probes against the tennis cv's that remain it's done yeah i don't think bion can do much
else here there is even like now observers back in the base of sos he's going to be able to
finally defend against those widow mines i think sos has just done it he's going to be a three one
lead in his best of seven poor bion man he's one time he tries something different yeah and he
just gets hit by that he's actually playing ladder terran right now which is if i put all my command
centres in corners maybe i'll win liberator's going to come in and try and do some damage but the
sport and overcharge the stalkers gg sos takes another map and he has one victory away from crowning
himself and tell extreme masters champion once again good god who stops him i think bion can but
he's gonna he's gonna have to be a little bit more fortunate here with some of his his build all the
choice and the way the game goes just in general so crazy so crazy like again i think you said it
when bion tries to do something a little bit different he gets whacked in the face by a proxie robo
and he has nothing back at home just unfortunate of events i feel that even if he is going to do
something different i want it to be something different than a widow mine opener i think a widow
mine opener is just not hitting home here for him at all the thing is though if he was something
different then like play a commencing refers into like very greedy third commencing that's also
a massive gamble like you get the wrong hand of that you know what actually like i feel like sos
calculates everything so well that the one time you have finally tried that he hasn't dissipated
in a kill suit anyway you just can't win cannot believe and level up crest is gonna be our next map
here bion right now getting run over the master of mind games sos from championship to championship
is just getting the better end of every single engagement is liberally in the mind as well as on
the battlefield what he's supposed to do june has already done it recently he he'd be sos
2 0 in the ssl qualifier so he's gonna have to find some of that will power that he had recently and
maybe a little bit of good fortune definitely will help as well because again like this this kind
of situation you just saw like when it happens to you it definitely leaves like a soul taste in
in your throat like it's yeah was not ideal for sure even though like you know as a tern here
you know the pro the proto so pannan doesn't have detection back at home but you never gonna have
enough back at home we just the marines and the scvs against a proto as smart as sos that can just
kite back and the war prism you know everybody talks about the adept and all good it is but the war
prism being able to pick up units from so far away so pixie d.a. so good yeah really is just say
about a drop them and get back going all right okay so let's get into this down to the bottom
left hand corner he is one game away from complete elimination it is x teams peel
young i can't get away from doing done a one and because you said he doing a do reassles so you
you screwed yourself and maybe and up to the top right hand corner we have our blue
protoss representing jenna green wings it is s os playing so well like i can't believe the series
we've had today they've been great series every single one of them again though with
a pretty early scouts not the not maybe not as fast as we saw earlier here from ss and bion
is traditional early gas here do we see bion playing something really different here i feel like he
he almost has to to be honest he needs to change something up sure he tried last game with
the proxy didn't work but still if we keep some playing the same as he's been it's just gonna be
so hard i feel for bion to be able to pull it off and ss actually opening double gateway here
interesting with double gas so he's not gonna go for any kind of early game nexus not probable
eventually go over there he put bion to complete that wall off he might be afraid that bion
tries for something like a one based all in which on this map can be really really strong
bion is gonna send his s cv out as well whilst this command center goes down we saw
eutomo actually on this very map against t drogo a dream hack semi finals try for one base build
which back then was defended but that doesn't mean it can't outwork it can be very very strong so ss
maybe a little bit wary of that wanted to play a little bit more on the safer side of things so
opening with the double gateway here is gonna be able to go for double stalkers on the map where
i've talked about this earlier when we saw it played in pvp the natural is very very white there is
no bunker that you can make on this natural that will cover all of it so if you go for double stalker
like this and a modorship core you have a lot of potential to do quite a bit of damage i wonder if
ss wants to go for some sort of proxy as well with it like maybe something like a robo or if you
want to maybe throw down some pion to go for some overcharging to go with this
i see vina gonna fortunately pay for it so oh wait
he didn't see that pylon down towards the bottom yeah absolutely i wonder what this is
exactly though oh actually wait ss in the msi mga over in theater when he played innovation in semi finals
hmm he had this great one base blink which we don't see anymore and nobody would ever expect
so not opening the way he has on the map like this where there is so much room around the main
to blink into it yeah over there you can first go into pylon and overcharge them and kill as
much as you can actually this is gonna get shut down because he messed up but yeah he can just open
with some aggression here and then behind this go oh it's a dark shrine uh oh i thought he might
be blinked but maybe because the pylon got sniped here he was like all right it's gonna be harder
well then suppose to go for a lot of stalker stuff close to that position so i'm gonna go for
that shrine he's not gonna expect that kill the brook oh okay let's go and get another pylon down here
oh that's what what's all widow mine oh good job buddy you've you've paid for yourself now
but i think honestly like this if he had if he was going for blink right now this would be three
two already i would just say like it's over but the fact that sos is going for dt's gives him a
serious chance to still win this because john i feel like he might not be able to anticipate that
yeah now sos does need a proxy pylon here to start very very soon
will be on get any bay will his canis open his base probably not because it's a very low econ game
he wants to spam those mules here yeah and he's gonna be about can he have a scan on time
and more scans down the line to defend his ddts here and behind this sos does go for blink
i still see another pylon being proxy to forwards here does beyond as he's trying to go for that
counter drop place of what is going on shades gonna head down in oh actually could have gone in
yeah they just stopped for some reason oh yeah actually goes up to the high ground for the
bit oh that's a big deal actually killing that if you could kill the the addon here yeah
there's then dts tries to get what he can but doesn't in the end there's two dot time plus gonna walk
in he has energy for a scan and the less i wonder actually what dts are gonna go for i guess like
the depot and then the greens maybe well get center here and there's actually really not much to
deal with that so did he did he was not going into the into the main here was it lowered wow and that's
not good that's gonna escape no oh my god it's got what won't help that would help i can't believe
this he survives wow so bune's gonna evacuate out there there's more scans but not s always
gonna be the one on two bases a raven starts that's so brilliant oh love it take lab on the
stopboard with a mine honestly like this is still good for bune i think even though ss somehow
it's gonna have a natural yeah i mean like there you go gg better be crazy one those dts not quite
able to do enough they they durp a little bit if they are moved straight up the ramp taken out the
depot and then started spreading all in the main maybe they could have done enough but i feel like
maybe beyond sense this was coming because yet quite a bit of the energy on the cc's you do spam
you also didn't panic yet enough to scan on time pushback the dts even though you didn't get the
staff on the first one i mean how much of a difference would there have even been like in the
start i gave him a mnemonicia call hadn't died well with a mine and that pylon walls up and he
out the photo charge that all started as well with that first probe dying plus the bottom being
canceled like that's not supposed to happen you're supposed to wait for your stalkers and mnemonicia
call to be there to cover these units and then you make double triple pylon down that ramp
take out the entire world that's there yeah yeah with the i guess even the barrack like might have
to fly back against this and then behind this it's open season for those dts to walk in there and do
all the damage show ss clearly butchered the execution here crazy crazy games if it's not like the
really long drawn out games it's the small kind of smaller aggressive games that was just all over
the place really a little bit hard to track some of the aggression that was going on i think you
should he could have he could have killed the reactor as well like at some points and then they
would have been less marines to properly defend against the dts but didn't go for it
all right we're just waiting now for game number six to begin central protocol will be our map
of all maps central protocol
oh
done definitely uh needs to be thinking how near about what to do because it's three two four ss
ss is one map away here from winning the whole tournament and there is uh no room for any mess up
here in terms of build order like everything scouting and since we're going to be heading into central
protocol which definitely gonna be one of those maps where john i think has potential to make
something good happen here but ss has shown how he can use some of these maps that are supposed to
be these advantages for proto sometimes because he can be harder to take a third base he's shown
how he can use that with advantage with multiple ghost gold base player on pryon terraces earlier
are we gonna see something like that again let us find out the under the bottom left we have our
red turran representing x team it is pion
getting himself back in this maybe but he has to win two from here on out and then up to the top
right hand corner we have our blue pro sauce representing junei green wings it is s os
i hear the cheer count and i yeah the screaming girls are wow wow just to say the links
to how do we want to open here no gas yet from john ok he goes for it now
and ss still with a fairly early scout now you know i've talked about how this is a map where it
can be really really hard to take a third base do we see against something crazy out of ss
like something like a gold base very quickly the thing is on this map is definitely going to be
much harder to pull it off than early on pryon terraces because he would be very far away from his
main base so i feel like probably not but maybe some kind of two base plays but she sees it's already
up by one game here and only one game away from winning the whole thing the thing is though if
ss tries that and he fails he loses momentum here adding to the last map of this series i always feel
as a ss is the kind of player that once he does get a very very strongly like a 31 for example
he's willing to just throw straight after strapped to strad someone because he has games in hand
and then in the last game he would play something out really really long but i mean that could happen
again we'll see there's another part i'm going down to the extremity of this map right now of his
base by the way you realize what map he's left right after this arena oh god oh god
forgot one base then based that would be so amazing that would be so sick
oh well we'll see but for now what is sss going to do double stalker production already to start
things off at least same be able to last game so far now do we see again something like a twilight
actually like if you were to go for something like blink here it could be pretty good
gonna proxy oh i think proxy robo on a map like this where there is rocks at the back door
this could be really really good here for uh for sss i can't i can't imagine you know world though
where beyond doesn't know about this bill and doesn't scount for it and i feel like this is what
is scv is for you across the map oh it's these two stalkers probably already know something's up
he's gonna start a bunker and actually this bill is so insanely strong i'm really worried for
be on right now yeah i mean the thing is is that even if there is a bunker at the front
he can still actually just he's gonna have a war prison with it again he can just ferry those
units up he needs to make sure that this probe isn't spotted coming from the bottom of costs so
otherwise it just would be ins to be scouted he starts to start port anyway here will be on he
starts to widow mine as well i i think like a cyclone would have been a better choice here against this
more man whoop loads in that bunker gets on out of there proxying in the hall of fame here is sss
so we do have the robot about to finish up get things going
hmm actually okay it's gonna go for the immortal this time instead of a quick war prism that we saw
earlier out of ss so i'm gonna look back differently i really think that he might just want to
burst down that those rocks this back door and then just run right in there and then just try to
finish the game pretty much immediately yeah some good guiding because how would you shut this down
without bunkers if you don't have a bunker in the right locations how do you shut it out i think you
need like a bunch of tanks uh if you have tanks plus many vaks actually you can pick up the tanks
bring them back so it's not like they're gonna be sitting ducks against the immortals like
we're gonna be taking them taking them out very quickly so it's the bunker he's he might try and go
the ramp here like as a as a sort of mind game there's a widow mind there but it'd be careful
oh you're the proxies okay actually with the prox second oh my god i can't believe this uh oh
this is really bad there's another widow mind there as well though try to split up one of the
stalkers only one stalker takes proper damage to that observer is gonna de-mind the field here with
that one single widow mind oh my god pretty much instantly ss is gonna be right on top of that
barrack he can basically kite endlessly and he's gonna re-walk a lot of stalkers here behind
he says well he's gonna lose so much of his production if that barrack goes down he has to
actually keep that life the scb's of come off line one of them is gonna repair but there's not
really that many marines the move we know i know the back has to catch his itself a stalker as well
but this is still 21 arms to play against 13 liberators about the pop he tries to get the barracks
out of there but it's gonna die he's gonna lose so much production from this and he hardly has
anything left scb's come off the line as well once again there's not that many marines to hold on
against ss oes here who has bust down the doors he is bringing this home and the liberator is
gonna try and stop this but it's gonna get focused down as well there's so oes here with this
potential victory trying to focus down the medevac as well there is not much left here at all
forbion it's been a great tournament for him so far but you don't defeat the champion you do not
defeat the world champion here with a sea shank going down as well s os has run rampant the
scango's down in his base he sees everything that's going on back there and that is gg s os
crowns himself the intel extreme masters champion once again here in Taipei representing jinei green
wings with style what a champion what a champ absolutely made the all defense happy here a lot of
different builds some very aggressive ones some very actually either very video very aggressive
no middle ground here for this guy who is gonna stop s os from taking championship after
championship like a sea of the void tea takes another trophy let's head over to the analysis desk
to hear what the boys have to say about mr dole sign or dole sign thank you very much calora s os
picks up another trophy seems unstoppable when he plays in these tournaments he just turns up and says
all right this one i think i'm gonna win this and he does pick and he played in such a way where it
was really both ends of the the scale really it was complete greeting one set of games and then
the next funeral he just went all right well this guy's gonna finish this guy's gonna die very
fast and he went all in all in all in until he broke him technically maybe not the most uh you know
superior player in terms of every little detail of his micro and macro but when it comes down to
the strategy the decision making this guy is an absolute god s os he just came out like you said
alternating that extreme greed that extreme aggression he chose the right builds and he put all
the pressure on beyond there he said i am just gonna keep applying this pressure i'm gonna force
you to make mistakes and if you don't really step up to the plate like i'm just gonna use all of
that experience from all those championships i've won and i'm gonna i'm gonna push you over really
well played by s os i think uh one thing to say here claus and taut is he's got a bit of practice
we've lifted up trophies he's picked up the world championship trophy and that thing is not as heavy
no that must be an easy job from up there yeah very much so i look at look at how that series play
now i i mean as you said pick just crazy wild variations from game to game and that robo build
that robo build looks scary as anything actually it's funny like at the end of the series you kept
asking who's gonna defeat this guy and now you guys mentioned the trophy i know who could defeat
s was the champagne the champagne that's pretty much it no yeah that that's way too easy from up
there no but a dominating performance from him this weekend he's not very good obviously the
most difficult game was against hero which was back and forth for sure but overall a very good
performance from s os pick yeah i mean he came out and he showed that he has what it takes
some people were doubting him a few of us were doubting him saying you know he's had a bit of a
shaky start to legacy but as we can see as time goes on he's just getting his footing more and more
and already taking a championship this early on it's such a great start to the year for him so i
think 2016 is just gonna be absolutely huge he had a lot of good fortune but it feels like s os
creates his own luck he's not just pure luck where he's like rolling the dice even though sometimes
it might seem like it and beyond on the other hand i feel like i'm gonna expect a lot more out of
him you know in the in the future i hope he attends a lot more tournaments and we keep on seeing him
because he was a very entertaining player that also played very well this tournament even though he
lost in grand finals yeah i really got to echo that sentiment i would love to see more of
dual see uh sorry Bjorn why do i care that that's because he said it in the real souls yeah it's all
it's pretty weird Bjorn's cool Bjorn's also kind of cool i like Bjorn he's a nice guy that's
what i'm done you like to see him all this year obviously and uh you know a good performance
good to see him come to another international event thank you very much gentlemen i had a lot of
fun broadcasts in this event for you guys back at home that's it us done here in Taipei before we
go though do make sure to check out the plays dot tv plugin for all the highlights of this tournament
if you've missed any and if you upload a highlight and get it into the top 25 for this event you
may find yourself winning an event tickets the inter extreme masters in catavits where the world
championship series winter championship will be taking place that's all for us here on the desk
at the inter extreme masters in Taipei we'll see you next time
bye